<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>RYAN LUU'S ACTIVITY SHEET</title>
    <description>My activity sheet is a daily log of my work, process, and thoughts.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 00:11:17 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2017 00:11:17 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.3.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Dancing at Visarts</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;post-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/CKCY4HR.jpg&quot;/&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Tonight was memorable. Kristina coordinated her company's holiday party and it was a blast.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/g6C1TDb.jpg&quot;/&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/71MpCMJ.jpg&quot;/&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;I'm very proud of her!&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;It was nice to be a guest at an event for once.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;p.s. I did get the my personal site working in gulp as well 😁.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/14/Day14.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/14/Day14.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Read more, read more, read more.</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;post-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/MK3pW1I.png&quot;/&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Part of the reason I love having an activity sheet is that it holds me accountable to the goals I set.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;One of my goals is to read more and when my friend Andrew recommended these two books to me today, it seemed like a great opportunity to commit.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;I've purchased the first one 'Cracking the PM Interview' as an amazon kindle e-read and I'm going to try and read it on my phone while I'm at the gym.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;I read the first few pages and I can tell that it going to be a good read.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/12/Day12.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/12/Day12.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>How to become a better Product Manager?</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;post-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/e2QTV9v.png&quot;/&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Being a product manager is my true role. I love driving products from concept to reality by connecting business, development, and design.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;But defining my role as a product manager can be difficult at times because every circumstance need something different. I am constantly having to adapt to the needs of my product, market, and teammates while balancing both budget and time.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;So I spent some time today researching more about how other people define the role of a product manager and the techniques they use to optimize their effectiveness.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;I found a lot of stuff, but one thing that I really like is this graphic.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/bbMdbCR.jpg&quot;&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;It does a very good job of breaking down the areas a PM is involved with and the responsibilities within each area of focus.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;I'm going to continue to soak up more knowledge and use the insights to start applying for roles as a PM.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/11/Day11.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/11/Day11.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Learning Gulp and first development for my portfolio</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;post-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/VjgtRnB.gif&quot;/&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Gulp is a javascript task runner that helps automate tasks like bundling code and minifying images/gifs etc.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Because my personal site will have a lot of heavy imagery, I decided to use gulp to build my personal site so that it's fast and snappy.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;I like it's plugin/modular infrastructure and the fact that it uses sass by default.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;On another note, the site design continues to change as I show people and get feedback. I'm think I'm goint to adjust my user flow so that there are individual pages for each project.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;It's cool to see how it changes day over day.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/10/Day10.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/10/Day10.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Updated design/experience for my personal site</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;post-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/Z30ER69.png&quot;/&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;I spent time today refining the purpose, vision, and design for my personal site.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Highlighting my frontend work is a priority, so I've made it easy to access my work from a fixed sidebar on the right.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;I'm also going to make the images interactive. When a visitor hovers over one of the designs, it will trigger an accompanying video that will show engagements like hover to play or chopping a video.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;It is definitely a thought provoking process breaking down what's important and I'm excited to see it take shape.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/09/Day9.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/09/Day9.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Conducting problem interviews for Stash</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;post-container&quot;&gt;

    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Products need to solve problems. Whether it's telling you the time or autonomously driving you to work, products are created to solve a human problem.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Today, Osebo and I interviewed a bio-med engineering masters student named Mishi.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/aRv0Pzb.gif&quot;/&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;She was super nice and gave us a lot of great insight into her daily experience of discovering and saving online. Her go-to service is/was Tumblr, but it's gotten really cluttered and difficult for her to easily revisit her favorite content.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;The conversation was extremely helpful in identifying where her painpoints lie and how we can shape Stash's experience to solve her problems.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Talking with Mishi also gave us a better understanding of who our target audience is. I'm not going to draw any conclusions yet, but we're excited to conduct more interviews to see if there are any consistent patterns.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/08/Day8.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/08/Day8.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Collecting facts on climate change for an interactive infographic</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;post-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/zCgAoLk.jpg&quot;/&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;One topic that has captured my attention recently is global warming. There is so much controversy surrounding the issue, but there is no denying that human carbon emissions are causing alarming outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Even though climate change has been gaining media coverage, people still seem to be unaware of the long term consequences from our current carbon output or don't care enough to make changes in their daily lives.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/9qtGfmN.jpg&quot;/&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;I want to do my part to help inform others about the realities of global warming by creating a interactive inforgraphic about climate change.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;I've started collecting research and here are some of the mind-boggling facts that I found:&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Every single day, 70 million tons of carbon dioxide are released into the earth’s atmosphere. That’s 1.4 billion pounds – yesterday, today, tomorrow... &lt;a href=&quot;https://thinkprogress.org/al-gore-nyu-law-9-18-06-60acdb2cb08f#.5szwf7emr&quot;&gt;[1]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Since temperature record-keeping began in 1880, the 10 warmest years on record have been in the past 12 years. &lt;a href=&quot;http://data.giss.nasa.gov/gistemp/2008/&quot;&gt;[2]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;20 million tons of ice are lost per day from just one glacier in Greenland. This amount of daily ice lost is equal to the amount of water that New York City uses in an entire year. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.huffingtonpost.com/al-gore/a-generational-challenge_b_113359.html&quot;&gt;[3]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Over a hundred million people will be displaced by just a 1-yard rise in sea levels. Many scientists predict that the oceans will rise at least this much by 2100. &lt;a href=&quot;http://news.nationalgeographic.com/news/2004/12/1206_041206_global_warming.html&quot;&gt;[4]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;I don't want my children and grandchildren to never experience snow, or to have to wear medicical masks just to prevent them from inhaling smog. We only have one Earth, lets make changes to keep it habitable for future generations.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/HYcazGR.gif&quot;/&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/07/Day7.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/07/Day7.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Back to the drawing board for my personal site</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;post-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/Dpfprkv.jpg&quot;/&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;I realized that I got ahead of myself with my first crack at my personal site.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Osebo suggested that I take more time to think through the purpose of my personal site and to sketch multiple iterations before touching the computer.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;My goals with my personal site are to:&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Showcase my web work through individual case studies.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Convey my multi-disciplinary background and experience.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Capture viewers attention and entice them to contact me.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Keep things minimal while adding my own personal flare.&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Use a new Javascript library to create a unique interactive.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;I also think I'm going to build my personal site in gulp.js. I've never used it before, but I know it's fast and I've heard good things.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/06/Day6.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/06/Day6.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Making music discovery less cloudy with Rainbow</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;post-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Osebo, Sid, and I started building an easy way to see what your friends are liking on Soundcloud called Rainbow.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Over the past 2 weeks we've interviewed a variety of people to understand how they use Soundcloud and if they are interesting in seeing what their friends are listening to. Most if not all said yes, so we are building it.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/yN8IPg4.gif&quot;/&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;caption&quot;&gt;landing_interation_01&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;This is the first iteration of the landing page that I whipped up today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/05/Day5.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/05/Day5.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Revamping my personal site</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;post-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;My personal site is in need of a face lift, so I spent some time today mocking up a few design interations in Sketch.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/zjQYLCt.png&quot;&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;caption&quot;&gt;personal site mockup&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;I want to make it minimal while still conveying my diverse breadth of experience.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;This design seems a little overwhelming. I need to take more time to think out the userflow.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Sidenote, I'm back in the hospital with my girlfriend again. I might have to make this place my second office ⍨.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/04/Day4.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/04/Day4.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
