<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>RYAN LUU'S ACTIVITY SHEET</title>
    <description>My activity sheet is a daily log of my work, process, and thoughts.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 09:13:15 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 09:13:15 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.3.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Vimeo Experiment</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;post-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;On Tuesday, I have a interview with Vimeo for a Creative Technologist position with a focus on their video player. I'm excited!&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;I have a lot of experience working with YouTube's player, but I haven't tried with Vimeo's yet. I thought it would be a cool challenge to see if I could recreate hover to play viewing with Vimeo's player.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/nyFkUjZ.png&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;I'm setting a deadline for Monday. Time to get it done.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/02/03/Day34.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/02/03/Day34.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>More info in item overlay</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;post-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Osebo and I spent time today trying to figure out how we can show additional information about each item after it's opened.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;He can up with a few designs and the one that we decided to build looks like this.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/Jwb1I2v.png&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;It seems pretty straight forward, but it is extremely hard to get the block on the right to scale appropriately when the content on the left varies in size.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;I'm hoping to find a way to make it work, but we may need to redesign the more info block.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/UTuFXLt.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/nXxsrCD.jpg&quot;/&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/02/02/Day33.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/02/02/Day33.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Consulting before building the wrong thing</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;post-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;This past month I mentioned that I had acquired a new client that is looking to build a livestreaming video platform for webroadcasts and webinars.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;We've spent the past few weeks outlining a scope of work and digging into the details to develop a full understanding of the company vision as well as what's required to get to an MVP.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;After multiple sessions of ironing out the specifics, it became apparent that the best path to success wasn't to just start building an inflexible demo, but to do more research to find a scaleable solution.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;In this case, we found that instead of using a two solutions tied together with hard code, that an end-to-end technology is a better solution that reduces complexity and offers additional benefits in the form of analytics and integrations.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;It's great to have the chance to work directly with clients in my pursuit to become a better Product Manager. I've learned that it is extremely important to fully comprehend a client's vision and goals before moving into the design/build process. It saved me weeks of time and prevented them from wasting money on a semi-useful product that wouldn't scale.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/02/01/Day32.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/02/01/Day32.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Checking off tickets at WeWork</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;post-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;I took a trip downtown to tour two different WeWork offices today. The first one was near the White House and the other was in Dupont Circle.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/02OHHnq.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;It was nice to work in a new environment and I was able to check off all but one of my tickets on the sprint board. Another plus was being able to get feedback from random people in the coworking space.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;I'm not sure if it makes sense for me to commit to the coworking space at this point, but I'm going to sleep on it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/31/Day31.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/31/Day31.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>One week sprints for a better workflow</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;post-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;The needs of each team change over time and as a product manager it's my job to make decisions to improve the effectiveness of the team's workflow.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;With all of our team members having full time commitments (jobs, school, clients), our building process with Stash has been divided and inconsistent. This has led to a gap between design and development where neither side is aware of what the other is working on. We have a sprint board for development, but the design work hasn't been tracked.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Our team needs a better way to keep track of all of our work in one place so we can set goals together, log our work, and hold each other accountable. The solution is to include design objectives to our sprint board and shorten the sprints to one week.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/oF0yjbH.png&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;I'm excited to see how this improves our workflow. Grind time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/30/Day30.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/30/Day30.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The High Line and The Whitney Museum</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;post-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Continuing our adventure in New York, we walked the High Line this morning.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/8fG7DJj.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/gmWrk2G.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/CWRL7Sw.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;And visited the Whitney in the afternoon.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/h8rXkIL.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/EGSM3g7.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/4qiiR7B.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/dNTkZEK.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/CW4WGg1.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;The trip to NYC was a blast; can't wait to do more exploring soon!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/29/Day29.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/29/Day29.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Blue Man Group in NYC</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;post-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;I traveled up to New York this morning for a weekend in Manhattan.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Kristina and I walked through Times Square/Central Park and ended the day by seeing the Blue Man Group at Astor Theatre. Here are a couple pics.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/ZASUr14.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/QDPeRrd.jpg?1&quot;/&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/28/Day28.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/28/Day28.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Museum view in React</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;post-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;My web work day got shortened because I went to work as a photographer tonight in DC.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;One of the things I was learning about before I left was how to create a museum view for Stash's cards. The main problem with the current version is that items are added in columns instead of in rows. The only way to get the items to position themselves in rows is to use a technique called Masonry.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/LUewtho.gif&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;There are plugins that enable this dynamic positioning in React that I will need to use to create this effect. That'll have to wait a couple days though because I'm headed to NYC with Kristina tomorrow morning 🗽!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/27/Day27.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/27/Day27.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Embodying the product manager mindset</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;post-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;I continue to read Cracking the PM Interview and many of the PMs interviewed in the book emphasize the importance of being constantly curious. I agree with this ideology and will push myself to learn something new everyday.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt; Today, I came across &lt;a href=&quot;http://designkit.org&quot;&gt;designkit.org&lt;/a&gt;. It's a fantastic resource for learning about human-centered design, crafted by IDEO.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;This is an intro video they created about human-centered design.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;iframe src=&quot;https://player.vimeo.com/video/106505300?title=0&amp;byline=0&amp;portrait=0&quot; width=&quot;640&quot; height=&quot;360&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;IDEO has also created some really insightful &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.designkit.org/methods&quot;&gt;design methods&lt;/a&gt; that are worth checking out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/26/Day26.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/26/Day26.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Committed to uncovering the truth</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;post-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;The truth is out there, but recently people with power have been using their influence to publicly dispute facts and create obstacles to make it difficult for citizens to access important information.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Osebo and I decided that we needed to do our part in helping people access fact based information on environmental, social, economic, and educational issues.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;We chose the name &quot;Hidden Info&quot; because we're committed to uncovering the truth. We'll strive to be unbiased and our writing will require a great deal of research and fact checking to ensure we put out is 100% truthful. We will be providing sources for our findings.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Today we whipped up a basic prototype just to get a sense for what we need to include in the experience.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/pAb2uqH.gif&quot;/&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/25/Day25.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/25/Day25.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
