<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>RYAN LUU'S ACTIVITY SHEET</title>
    <description>My activity sheet is a daily log of my work, process, and thoughts.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 03:34:17 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2017 03:34:17 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.3.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Making music discovery less cloudy with Rainbow</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;post-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Osebo, Sid and I started building an easy way to see what your friends are liking on Soundcloud called Rainbow.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Over the past 2 weeks we've interviewed a variety of people to understand how they use Soundcloud and if they are interesting in seeing what their friends are listening to. Most if not all said yes, so we are building it.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/yN8IPg4.gif&quot;/&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;caption&quot;&gt;landing_interation_01&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;This is the first iteration of the landing page that I whipped up today.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/05/Day5.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/05/Day5.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Revamping my personal site</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;post-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;My personal site is in need of a face lift, so I spent some time today mocking up a few design interations in sketch&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/PhfeHAv.png&quot;&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;caption&quot;&gt;homepage_interation_01&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/1R6e7OD.png&quot;&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;caption&quot;&gt;homepage_interation_02&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;I think I like the second one better. It's cleaner and allows for a scroll based user flow rather than a click heavy experience. I'll keep interating and posting my progressions.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Sidenote, I'm back in the hospital with my girlfriend again. I might have to make this place my second office ⍨.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/04/Day4.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/04/Day4.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Overnight stay in the hospital and building in Jekyll</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;post-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;http://imgur.com/cXuMjn6.gif&quot;&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;I didn't get any sleep last night. I was with my gf in the hospital overnight and it was pretty brutal.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Luckily, I brought my hotspot/laptop and while we were waiting I decided to rebuild my activity sheet in Jekyll per suggestion of Osebo.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Creating posts are sooo much easier and it improves the load efficiency significantly.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;We were having trouble getting the images in the yaml frontmatter to render on the homepage, but I was able to figure it out. It makes the homepage way more appealing.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;I'm going to continue to push myself to experiment with new programming languages this year. Some of the ones I'm currently interested in are Angular, Gulp and React. I'll keep buildings new things and will post them here.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/03/Day3.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/03/Day3.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Researching the psychology of collecting</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;post-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;http://imgur.com/5RiIotI.jpg&quot;&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;While working with Osebo on Stash today, we decided to dig into the true problem that we're attempting to solve with Stash. It started with a question. &lt;b&gt;Why do people collect things?&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text quote&quot;&gt;&quot;Collecting is a basic human instinct; a survival advantage amplified by eons of natural selection. Those of our ancient ancestors who managed to accumulate scarce objects may have been more prone to survive long enough to bear offspring.&quot; &lt;a class=&quot;source&quot; href=&quot;https://www.ha.com/intelligent-collector/why-do-we-collect-things.s?article=collect&quot;&gt;(source)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;http://imgur.com/2Xid92T.jpg&quot;&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;If you think about it, everyone collects something. Baseball cards, money, pictures, letters from loved ones, sneakers... something. Our motivations to collect stem from a few common reasons including:&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Knowledge and learning&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Relaxation and stress reduction&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Personal pleasure&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Social interaction with fellow collectors and others&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Competitive challenge&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Recognition by fellow collectors and perhaps even non-collectors&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;The desire to control, possess and bring order to part of the world&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Nostalgia and/or a connection to history&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Accumulation and diversification of wealth &lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;divider&quot;&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;So how does this apply to Stash? We feel like collecting content on the web is &lt;b&gt;difficult&lt;/b&gt;, &lt;b&gt;unappealing&lt;/b&gt;, and &lt;b&gt;hidden&lt;/b&gt; from others who can find value in it.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Right now, to collect webpages, images, videos, etc., people either: share links on chat platforms where they get lost in conversation, create bookmark folders that often get forgotten/cluttered, or build websites for their collection, which take a significant amount of time and effort to create/maintain.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Our goal is to make it easier for people to create, share, and discover collections of their favorite media.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/02/Day2.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/02/Day2.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>I'm making a daily activity sheet.</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;post-container&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;http://imgur.com/8FtI3o8.gif&quot;&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;To start 2017, my &lt;a href=&quot;http://brendanluu.github.io&quot;&gt;brother&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://osebo.github.io/activitysheet&quot;&gt;Osebo&lt;/a&gt; and I decided to make activity sheets to push ourselves to create new stuff everyday.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;I'll use this space to document the things I'm working on, share my ideas and record my journey.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Today I upgraded to a new '15 macbook 🙌🏼 . It's nice to start a new year with fresh hardware that will allow me to continue to improve my programming and design.&lt;/p&gt;
    &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;One of the things I'm looking forward to most in 2017 is building &lt;a href=&quot;http://stash.ag&quot;&gt;Stash&lt;/a&gt;. Osebo, Diego and I have been working hard and will be relasing an MVP soon. Off to the races.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/01/Day1.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/01/01/Day1.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
