<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>RYAN LUU'S ACTIVITY SHEET</title>
    <description>My activity sheet is a daily log of my work, process, and thoughts.</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2017 11:14:28 -0500</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2017 11:14:28 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.3.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rainbow V1</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;post-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Sid, Osebo and I were able to get a MVP version of Rainbow working!&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/t8A0rth.gif&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;It's been quite a challenge due to a couple unforseen constraints. The primary one is the inability to build and make changes locally. In order for the experience to work, the user must authenticate with soundcloud's api.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Despite the roadblocks, we've been able to get a list of people you follow and when you select someone, it shows their soundcloud likes via embeds. Soundcloud's embeds are pretty load heavy so we've implemented lazy loading to reduce load times.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Next we're looking at creating our own soundcloud player so we don't need to rely on the embeds and can create a more fluid experience where songs play in successsion.
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/02/12/Day43.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/02/12/Day43.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Exhausting photography double</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;post-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;I really enjoy sharing updates on the things I'm building, but somedays it isn't so glamorous.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Today, I worked a double for my photography job and was out of the house from 9am to 1am. It was long, and tiring.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;BUT, I can't complain because this job gives me the flexibility to focus my energy on creating during the work week.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 11 Feb 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/02/11/Day42.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/02/11/Day42.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Forshow landing layer</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;post-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Forshow's landing page needed an update now that we're changing the brand, so I worked with Osebo to create a new experience.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/Il3XLfq.gif&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;There are some concerns about hiding the examples at first and we will likely reorganize the message to show the examples upfront. More to come.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/02/10/Day41.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/02/10/Day41.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Rainbow's first working UX</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;post-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Rainbow is a side project to help people discover music their friends are listening to. Osebo, Sid and I worked to put together the first working UX.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/j1S4q3k.gif&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Users sign in with their SoundCloud account and Rainbow shows a list of the people they are following. When a user clicks on one of their friends, their friend's liked songs from SoundCloud will display in the feed.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;A working demo will be ready by this weekend.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/02/09/Day40.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/02/09/Day40.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>New Nav &amp; Add Link</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;post-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Today I spent time rebuilding the navigation for Forshow; including a new design of the add item form.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/k5rlSUQ.gif?1&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Below the nav bar, we have added a user profile block. For an anonymous user it will have a smiley face and once they log in it will show their username and have the ability to add a photo (which we still need to build).&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;It's coming together, but there are still a lot of things to get done in this sprint.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/02/08/Day39.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/02/08/Day39.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Lazy loading and a potential new brand</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;post-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;I started working on a lazy loading feature for Stash that would optimize loading efficiency for the experience and more importantly reduce the amount of calls we make to iframely. The more calls we make the more money we pay, so this is an important improvement.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Osebo and I have also been trying to figure out a new brand identify for Stash because of the confusion that's created by other companies that have the same name.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Today we came up with forshow.co. I actually really like it. Creating collections for showing other people is the goal, so the name makes a lot of sense.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/aXfDjRG.png&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Side note, I had my phone interview today and I have been invited to a second round interview 😀!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 07 Feb 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/02/07/Day38.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/02/07/Day38.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Deployed a new Stash</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;post-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;The Stash team finished our one week sprint today with a successful deployment to our testing server. User signup/login in now working along with a new design of the items and item overlays.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/XCUrepk.png&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Getting both design and development back together on the sprint board was very effective in helping the team stay on track and we were able to set clear objectives for the next week.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;We have a collage view in the pipeline that will replace the grid view and we're finishing up profiles so users can truly create their own stashes. In the meantime, checkout the latest version &lt;a href=&quot;http://staging.stash.ag&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Feb 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/02/06/Day37.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/02/06/Day37.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Legendary Comeback</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;post-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;Superbowl Sunday is basically a holiday in the US, but I did have a photography gig this morning in Baltimore. Luckily it ended at 4pm, so I was still able to participate in the Superbowl festivities.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;The game was between the Atlanta Falcons &amp; the New England Patriots. The first three quarters of the game were all Atlanta with the Falcons holding a 28 to 3 lead at one point.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;But some how, Tom Brady led his team back in the 4th quarter to tie the game at 28, force overtime, and drive down the field in overtime to score a game winning touchdown to win his 5th Superbowl. Epic.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/ufH5AhR.jpg&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;It goes to show that the greatest winners in life, never give up no matter how grim the situation looks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/02/05/Day36.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/02/05/Day36.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Completed the Vimeo Demo</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;post-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;I finished the Vimeo hover to play demo this morning.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/0oXFMZ2.gif?1&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;I'm really  happy with how it came out! You can try the experience for yourself &lt;a href=&quot;http://rtluu.github.io/vimeodemo&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; (web only*).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/02/04/Day35.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/02/04/Day35.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Vimeo Experiment</title>
        <description>&lt;div class=&quot;post-container&quot;&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;On Tuesday, I have a interview with Vimeo for a Creative Technologist position with a focus on their video player. I'm excited!&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;I have a lot of experience working with YouTube's player, but I haven't spent much time working with Vimeo's player yet. I thought it would be a cool challenge to see if I could recreate hover to play viewing with Vimeo's player.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;img src=&quot;http://i.imgur.com/nyFkUjZ.png&quot;/&gt;
  &lt;p class=&quot;text&quot;&gt;I'm not quite sure how difficult it's going to be, but it should be fairly straightforward.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/02/03/Day34.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2017/02/03/Day34.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>jekyll</category>
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
